While I'm very familiar
with you and your family,
I have no way of knowing if
you are familiar with who I am.
Are you aware of my existence?
Yes.
This is good.
Now, are you aware of the job I've
been ordered to carry out in France?
Yes.
Please tell me what you've heard.
I've heard
that the Führer has put you in charge
of rounding up the Jews left in France
who are either hiding
or passing for Gentile.
The Führer couldn't have
said it better himself.
But the meaning of your visit,
pleasant though it is,
is mysterious to me.
The Germans looked through my house
nine months ago for hiding Jews
and found nothing.
I'm aware of that.
I've read the reports of this area.
But like any enterprise,
when under new management,
there is always a slight
duplication of efforts,
most of it being a complete waste of
time, but needs to be done nevertheless.
I just have a few
questions, monsieur LaPadite.
If you can assist me with answers,
my department can close
the file on your family.
Now,
before the occupation, there were
four Jewish families in this area,
all dairy farmers like yourself.
Doleracs, Rollins, the Loveitts
and the Dreyfuses.
Is that correct?
To my knowledge,
those were the Jewish families
among the dairy farmers.
Herr Colonel, would it
disturb you if I smoked my pipe?
Please, monsieur LaPadite,
this is your house, make
yourself comfortable.
Now, according to these papers,
all the Jewish families in this
area have been accounted for
except the Dreyfuses.
Somewhere in the last year it
would appear they've vanished.
Which leads me to the conclusion that
they've either made good their escape
or someone is very
successfully hiding them.
What have you heard about the
Dreyfuses, monsieur LaPadite?
Only rumors.
I love rumors!
Facts could be so misleading,
where rumors, true or
false, are often revealing.
So, monsieur LaPadite,
what rumors have you heard
regarding the Dreyfuses?
Again, this is just a rumor,
but we heard the Dreyfuses
had made their way into Spain.
So, the rumors you've
heard have been of escape?
Yes.
Having never met the Dreyfuses,
would you confirm for me
the exact members of the
household and their names?
There were five of them.
The father, Jacob.
Wife, Miram.
And her brother, Bob.
How old is Bob?
Thirty, 31.
Continue.
And the children,
Amos
and Shosanna.
Ages of the children?
Amos was nine or 10.
And Shosanna?
And Shosanna was
18 or 19. I'm not really sure.
Well, I guess that should do it.
However, before I go, could I have
another glass of your delicious milk?
But of course.
Monsieur LaPadite,
are you aware of the nickname the
people of France have given me?
I have no interest in such things.
But you are aware of what they call me.
I'm aware.
What are you aware of?
That they call you "The Jew Hunter."
Precisely.
I understand your
trepidation in repeating it.
Heydrich apparently hates the moniker
the good people of Prague
have bestowed on him.
Actually, why he would hate the
name "the Hangman" is baffling to me.
lt would appear he has done
everything in his power to earn it.
Now I, on the other hand,
love my unofficial title
precisely because I've earned it.
The feature that makes me such an
effective hunter of the Jews is,
as opposed to most German soldiers,
I can think like a Jew
where they can only think like a German.
More
precisely, a German soldier.
Now, if one were to determine what attribute
the German people share with a beast,
it would be the cunning and the
predatory instinct of a hawk.
But if one were to determine what
attributes the Jews share with a beast,
it would be that of the rat.
The Führer and Goebbels' propaganda
have said pretty much the same thing.
But where our conclusions differ,
is I don't consider the
comparison an insult.
Consider for a moment
the world a rat lives in.
It's a hostile world, indeed.
If a rat were to scamper through
your front door, right now,
would you greet it with hostility?
I suppose I would.
Has a rat ever done anything to you
to create this animosity
you feel toward them?
Rats spread disease. They bite people.
Rats were the cause of the bubonic
plague, but that's some time ago.
I propose to you any
disease a rat could spread,
a squirrel could equally carry.
Would you agree?
Yet, I assume you don't share
the same animosity with squirrels
that you do with rats, do you?
No.
Yet, they're both rodents, are they not?
And except for the tail, they
even rather look alike, don't they?
It's an interesting
thought, Herr Colonel.
However interesting
as the thought may be,
it makes not one bit of
difference to how you feel.
If a rat were to walk in
here, right now, as I'm talking
would you greet it with a
saucer of your delicious milk?
Probably not.
I didn't think so.
You don't like them.
You don't really know
why you don't like them.
All you know is you find them repulsive.
Consequently, a German
soldier conducts a search
of a house suspected of hiding Jews.
Where does the hawk look?
He looks in the barn, he looks in
the attic, he looks in the cellar,
he looks everywhere he would hide.
But there are so many places it
would never occur to a hawk to hide.
However, the reason the Führer has
brought me off my Alps in Austria
and placed me in French cow country
today is because it does occur to me.
Because I'm aware what tremendous
feats human beings are capable of
once they abandon dignity.
May I smoke my pipe as well?
Please, Herr Colonel,
make yourself at home.
Now, my job dictates
that I must have my men enter your home
and conduct a thorough search
before I can officially cross
your family's name off my list.
And if there are any irregularities to
be found, rest assured they will be.
That is unless you have
something to tell me
that makes the conducting
of a search unnecessary.
I might add, also, that any information
that makes the performance of my duty
easier will not be met with punishment.
Actually, quite the contrary.
It will be met with reward.
And that reward will be,
your family will cease
to be harassed in any way
by the German military during the
rest of our occupation of your country.
You're sheltering enemies
of the state, are you not?
Yes.
You're sheltering them underneath
your floorboards, aren't you?
Yes.
Point out to me the areas
where they're hiding.
Since I haven't heard any disturbance,
I assume, while they're listening,
they don't speak English.
Yes.
I'm going to switch back to French now,
and I want you to follow my masquerade.
ls that clear?
Yes.
It's the girl.
Au revoir, Shosanna!
Ten-hut!
My name is Lieutenant Aldo Raine.
And I'm putting together a special
team, and I need me eight soldiers.
Eight Jewish American soldiers.
Now, you all might've heard rumors
about the armada happening soon.
Well, we'll be leaving
a little earlier.
We're going to be dropped into
France dressed as civilians.
Once we're in enemy territory,
as a bushwhacking guerrilla army,
we're going to be doing one
thing and one thing only.
Killing Nazis.
I don't know about you all,
but I sure as hell didn't come down
from the goddamn Smoky Mountains,
cross 5,000 miles of water,
fight my way through half of Sicily
and jump out of a fucking airplane to
teach the Nazis lessons in humanity.
Nazi ain't got no humanity.
They're the foot soldiers of a
Jew-hating, mass-murdering maniac
and they need to be destroyed.
That's why any and every son of a
bitch we find wearing a Nazi uniform,
they're going to die.
Now, I'm the direct descendent
of the mountain man Jim Bridger.
That means I got a little lndian in me.
And our battle plan will be
that of an Apache resistance.
We will be cruel to the Germans.
And through our cruelty,
they will know who we are.
And they will find the
evidence of our cruelty
in the disemboweled, dismembered
and disfigured bodies of their
brothers we leave behind us.
And the German won't be
able to help themselves
but imagine the cruelty their
brothers endured at our hands,
and our boot heels and
the edge of our knives.
And the German will be sickened by us.
And the German will talk about us.
And the German will fear us.
And when the German
closes their eyes at night
and they're tortured by their
subconscious for the evil they have done,
it will be with thoughts of
us that they are tortured with.
Sound good?
Yes, sir!
That's what I like to hear.
But I got a word of warning
for all you would-be warriors.
When you join my command,
you take on debit.
A debit you owe me, personally.
Each and every man under my
command owes me 100 Nazi scalps.
And I want my scalps.
And all y'all will get me 100 Nazi scalps
taken from the heads of 100 dead Nazis.
Or you will die trying!
Hey, Hirschberg.
Send that Kraut sarge over.
You. Go.
Sergeant Werner Rachtman.
Lieutenant Aldo Raine.
Pleased to meet you.
You know what "sit down" means, Werner?
Yes. Then sit down.
How is your English, Werner?
Because if need be, we got a
couple of fellows who can translate.
Wicki here,
an Austrian-Jew, got the fuck out
of Munich while the getting was good.
Became American, got drafted,
come back to give y'all what for.
Another one up there you
might be familiar with.
Sergeant Hugo Stiglitz.
Heard of him?
Everybody in the German Army
has heard of Hugo Stiglitz.
The reason
for Hugo Stiglitz's celebrity
among German soldiers is simple.
As a German-enlisted man,
he killed 13 Gestapo officers.
Instead of putting
him up against a wall,
the High Command decided
to send him back to Berlin
to be made an example of.
Needless to say, once the
Basterds heard about him,
he never got there.
Sergeant Hugo Stiglitz?
Lieutenant Aldo Raine.
These are the Basterds.
Ever heard of us?
We just want to say we're
a big fan of your work.
When it comes to killing Nazis...
... I think you show great talent.
And I pride myself for having
an eye for that kind of talent.
But your status as a Nazi
killer is still amateur.
We all come here to see
if you want to go pro.
Can I assume you know who we are?
You're Aldo the Apache.
Werner, if you heard of us,
you probably heard we ain't in
the prisoner-taking business.
We in the killing Nazi business,
and, cousin, business is a-booming.
Oh, yeah.
Now, that leaves two
ways we can play this out.
Either kill you or let you go.
Whether or not you're going
to leave this ditch alive
depends entirely on you.
Up the road a piece, there's an orchard.
Besides you, we know there's another
Kraut patrol fucking around here somewhere.
If that patrol were to
have any crack shots,
that orchard would be a
goddamn sniper's delight.
So if you ever want to eat
a sauerkraut sandwich again,
you got to show me on this
here map where they are.
You got to tell me how many
they are, and you got to tell me
what kind of artillery
they're carrying with them.
You can't expect me to divulge information
that would put German lives in danger.
Well, now, Werner, that's where you're
wrong, because that's exactly what I expect.
I need to know about
Germans hiding in trees.
And you need to tell me. And
you need to tell me right now.
Now, just take that finger of yours
and point out on this here map
where this party is being held,
how many is coming and what
they brought to play with.
I respectfully refuse, sir.
Hear that?
Yes.
That's Sergeant Donny Donowitz.
You might know him
better by his nickname.
The Bear Jew.
Now, if you heard of Aldo the Apache,
you got to have heard about The Bear Jew.
I heard of The Bear Jew.
What did you hear?
Beats German soldiers with a club.
He bashes their brains in with
a baseball bat, what he does.
And, Werner, I'm going to
ask you one last goddamn time,
and if you still respectfully refuse,
I'm calling The Bear Jew over.
He's going to take that big bat of his,
and he's going to beat
your ass to death with it.
Now, take your
Wiener-schnitzel-licking finger,
and point out on this
map what I want to know.
Fuck you.
And your Jew dogs.
Actually, Werner, we're all
tickled to hear you say that.
Quite frankly, watching
Donny beat Nazis to death
is the closest we ever get
to going to the movies. Donny!
Yeah?
Got us a German here who
wants to die for country.
Oblige him.
Did you get that for killing Jews?
Bravery.
Yeah!
- Oh, no!
Donny!
Yeah, Donny!
About now I'd be shitting
my pants if I was you.
Teddy Fucking Williams
knocks it out of the park!
Fenway Park is on its feet
for Teddy Fucking Ballgame!
He went yard on that one, on
to fucking Lansdowne Street!
You!
Damn it, Hirschberg!
Donny, bring that other
one over here. Alive!
Get the fuck up! Batter
up. You're on deck!
Two hits. I hit you,
you hit the ground.
English?
Wicki.
Ask him if he wants to live.
Tell him to point out on
this map the German position.
Ask him how many Germans.
Around about 12.
What kind of artillery?
Now, when you report what happened here,
you can't tell them you told us
what you told us. They'll shoot you.
They're going to want to know why
you so special, we let you live.
So tell them, we let you live so you
could spread the word through the ranks
what's going to happen
to every Nazi we find.
Now that you've survived the war, when
you get home, what you going to do?
WlCKl: He's going to hug his mother.
Well, ain't that nice?
Ask if he's going to
take off his uniform.
He's going to burn it.
Yeah, that's what we
thought. We don't like that.
See, we like our Nazis in
uniforms. That way you can spot them.
Just like that.
But you take off that uniform, ain't
nobody going to know you's a Nazi.
And that don't sit well with us.
So I'm going to give you a little
something you can't take off.
You know, Lieutenant, you're
getting pretty good at that.
You know how you get to
Carnegie Hall, don't you?
Practice.
Au revoir, Shosanna!
At that time, 35
millimeter nitrate film was so flammable
that you couldn't even bring
a reel onto a streetcar.
Hey, you can't bring those
here on a public vehicle.
They're films, ain't they? Yes.
Then they're flammable. Go on, hop off.
Because nitrate film
burns three times faster than paper.
Shosanna has a collection
of over 350 nitrate film prints.
Right this way, Lieutenant.
Lieutenant Archie Hicox
reporting, sir.
General Ed Fenech. At ease, Hicox.
Drink?
If you offer me a scotch and plain water,
I could drink a scotch and plain water.
That-a-boy, Lieutenant. Make it
yourself like a good chap, will you?
The bar is in the globe.
Something for yourself, sir?
Whiskey. Straight. No junk in it.
lt says here that you
speak German fluently.
Like a Katzenjammer Kid.
And your occupation before the war?
I'm a film critic.
List your accomplishments.
Well, sir, such as they are,
I write reviews and articles for a
publication called Films and Filmmakers,
and I've had two books published.
Impressive. Don't be modest,
Lieutenant. What are their titles?
The first book was called
Art of the Eyes, the Heart and the Mind:
A Study of German Cinema in the '20s.
And the second one was called
Twenty-Four Frame da Vinci.
It's a sub textual film criticism study
of the work of German director G.W. Pabst.
What should we drink to, sir?
Well...
Down with Hitler.
All the way down, sir.
Yes.
Are you familiar with German
cinema under the Third Reich?
Yes. Obviously, I haven't seen any of
the films made in the last three years,
but I'm familiar with it.
Explain it to me.
Pardon, sir?
Well, this little escapade of ours requires
a knowledge of the German film industry
under the Third Reich. Explain
to me UFA under Goebbels.
Goebbels considers the films he's making
to be the beginning of a
new era in German cinema.
An alternative to what he considers
the Jewish-German intellectual
cinema of the '20s,
and the Jewish-controlled
dogma of Hollywood.
How's he doing?
Frightfully sorry, sir. Once again?
You say he wants to take on
the Jews at their own game.
Well, compared to, say, Louis B. Mayer,
how's he doing?
Quite well, actually.
Since Goebbels has taken over,
film attendance has steadily risen
in Germany over the last eight years.
But Louis B. Mayer wouldn't be
Goebbels' proper opposite number.
I believe Goebbels sees himself
closer to David O. Selznick.
Brief him.
Lieutenant Hicox, at this point and time
I'd like to brief you on Operation Kino.
Three days from now
Joseph Goebbels is throwing a gala
premiere of one of his new movies in Paris.
What film, sir?
The motion picture is
called Nation's Pride.
In attendance at this
joyous Germatic occasion
will be Goebbels, Goring, Bormann,
and most of the German High Command
including all high ranking officers
of both the SS and the Gestapo,
as well as luminaries of the
Nazi propaganda film industry.
The master race at play?
Basically, we have all our
rotten eggs in one basket.
The objective of Operation Kino,
blow up the basket.
And like the snows of
yesteryear, gone from this earth.
Jolly good, sir.
An American Secret Service outfit
that lives deep behind enemy lines
will be your assist.
The Germans call them the Basterds.
The Basterds. Never heard of them.
Whole point of the Secret Service,
old boy, you not hearing of them.
But the Jerries have heard of them,
because these Yanks have been them the devil.
You'll be dropped into France,
about 24 kilometers outside of Paris.
The Basterds will be waiting for you.
First thing, you'll go to a
little village called Nadine.
In Nadine, there's a
tavern called La Louisiane.
There you'll rendezvous with our
double agent. She'll take it from there.
She's the one who is going
to get you into the premiere.
It'll be you, her, and two
German-born members of the Basterds.
She's also made all the other
arrangements you're going to need.
How will I know her?
I suspect that won't be
too much trouble for you.
Your contact is Bridget von Hammersmark.
Bridget von Hammersmark?
The German movie
star is working for England?
Yes, for the last two years now.
One could even say that
Operation Kino was her brainchild.
Indeed.
Got the gist?
I think so, sir. Paris when it sizzles.
You didn't say the goddamn
rendezvous is in a fucking basement.
l didn't know.
You said it was in a tavern.
lt is a tavern.
Yeah, in a basement.
You know, fighting in a basement
offers a lot of difficulties.
Number one being, you're
fighting in a basement.
What if we go in there
and she's not even there?
We wait.
Don't worry. She's a British
spy. She'll make the rendezvous.
Stiglitz, right?
That's right, sir.
l hear you're pretty good with that.
You know, we're not looking
for trouble right now.
Simply making contact with our
agent. Should be uneventful.
However, the off chance I'm
wrong, things prove eventful,
I need to know we can all remain calm.
I don't look calm to you?
Well, now that you put it
like that, l guess you do.
This Jerry of yours, Stiglitz, not
exactly the loquacious type, is he?
ls that the kind of man
you need? Loquacious type?
Fair point, Lieutenant.
So you all get in trouble in
there, what are we supposed to do?
Make bets on how it all comes out?
If we get into trouble,
we can handle it.
But if trouble does happen,
we need you to make damn sure
no Germans, or French, for that
matter, escape from that basement.
If Frau von Hammersmark's cover is
compromised, the mission is kaput.
Speaking of Frau von Hammersmark, whose
idea was it for the deathtrap rendezvous?
She chose the spot.
Isn't that just dandy?
Look, she's not a military
strategist. She's just an actress.
You don't got to be Stonewall Jackson to
know you don't want to fight in a basement.
She wasn't picking a place to fight.
She was picking a place
isolated and without Germans.
Mmm.
Well, if this is it, old boy,
l hope you don't mind if I
go out speaking the King's.
By all means, Captain.
There's a special rung in hell reserved
for people who waste good Scotch.
Seeing as I may be rapping
on the door momentarily,
l must say, damn good stuff, sir.
Now, about this pickle
we find ourselves in.
lt would appear there's only
one thing left for you to do.
And what would that be?
Stiglitz.
Say auf Wiedersehen to your Nazi balls.
You outside. Who are you?
British? American?
What?
We're American.
What are you?
I'm a German, you idiot.
Speak English
pretty good for a German.
l agree.
So let's talk.
Okay, talk.
I'm a father.
My baby was born today. ln Frankfurt.
Five hours ago.
H is name is Max. We were in
here drinking, celebrating.
They're the ones that came in shooting
and killing. It's not my fault!
Okay! lt wasn't your fault.
What's your name, soldier?
Wilhelm.
Now, is there anybody alive on our side?
No. I'm alive!
Who's that?
ls the girl on your side?
Which girl?
Who do you think? Von Hammersmark.
Yeah, she's ours.
ls she okay?
Wilhelm!
She's been shot.
But she's alive.
Okay, Wilhelm.
What do you say we make us a deal?
What's your name?
Aldo.
Okay, Wilhelm, here's my deal.
You let me and one of my men come
down there and take the girl away.
No guns. No guns me, no guns you.
And we take the girl and
leave. It's that simple, Willi.
You go your way, we go ours.
And little Max gets to grow up
playing catch with his daddy.
So what do you say,
Willi? We got us a deal?
Aldo.
I'm here, Willi.
l want to trust you.
But...
But how can l?
What choice you got, son?
Okay, okay.
Aldo,
I'm going to trust you.
Come down.
Hey, Willi, what's with the machine
gun? l thought we had us a deal?
We still have a deal.
Now, get the girl and go.
Not so fast.
We only got a deal,
we trust each other.
And a Mexican standoff ain't trust.
You need guns on me for it
to be a Mexican standoff.
You got guns on us. You
decide to shoot, we're dead.
Up top, they got grenades. They
drop them down here, you're dead.
That's a Mexican standoff,
and that was not the deal.
No trust, no deal.
All right, Aldo.
Fine.
Just take that fucking traitor,
and get her out of my sight.
Not so goddamn fast, doc. Tell
him to go play with his dogs.
Before we yank that slug out you,
you need to answer a few questions.
Few questions about what?
About I got three men dead back there.
Why don't you try telling
us what the fuck happened?
The British officer blew his German
act and the Gestapo major saw it.
Before we get into who shot John,
why'd you invite my men to a rendezvous
in a basement with a bunch of Nazis?
l can see since you didn't
see what happened inside,
that the Nazis being
there must look odd.
Yeah, we got a word for
that kind of odd in English.
It's called suspicious.
Everybody needs to calm down.
You're letting your imagination
get the better of you.
You met the sergeant yourself. Willi.
You remember him, don't you?
Yeah, I remember him.
His wife had a baby tonight.
He had just become a...
He had just become a father!
His commanding officer gave him and
his mates the night off to celebrate.
The Germans being there was either a
trap set by me or a tragic coincidence.
It couldn't be both.
How'd the shooting start?
The Englishman gave himself away.
How'd he do that?
He ordered three glasses.
We order three glasses.
That's the German three.
The other looks odd.
Germans would and did notice it.
Okay, let's pretend
there were no Germans
and everything went exactly
the way it was supposed to.
What was the next step?
Tuxedos.
To get them into the premiere
wearing military uniforms
with all the military
there would've been suicide.
But going as members of
the German film industry,
they wear tuxedos and fit
in with everybody else.
I arranged for the tailor
to fit three tuxedos tonight.
How'd you intend to get
them in that premiere?
Hand me my purse.
Lieutenant Hicox was
going as my escort.
The other two were going as a
German cameraman and his assistant.
You still get us in that premiere?
You speak German better
than your friends? No.
Have I been shot? Yes!
I don't see me tripping the light
fantastique up a red carpet anytime soon.
Least of all, by tomorrow night.
However, there's
something you don't know.
There've been two recent
developments regarding Operation Kino.
One, the venue has been changed
from The Ritz to a much smaller venue.
Enormous change at the last
minute? That's not very Germatic.
Why the hell is Goebbels
doing stuff so damn peculiar?
It probably has something to
do with the second development.
Which is?
Der Fuhrer is attending the premiere.
Fuck a duck!
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking getting a whack
at planting old Uncle Adolf
makes this horse a different color.
What is that supposed to mean?
lt means you getting
us in that premiere.
I'm probably going to
end up losing this leg.
Bye-bye, acting career.
Fun while it lasted.
How do you expect me
to walk the red carpet?
Doggy doc's going to dig
that slug out your gam.
He's going to wrap it up in a cast,
and you got a good how-l-broke-my-leg-
mountain-climbing story.
That's German, ain't it? You all
like climbing mountains, don't you?
I don't. I like smoking, drinking
and ordering in restaurants.
But I see your point.
We fill you up with morphine
till it's coming out your ears
and just limp your little
ass up that reuge carpet.
I know this is a silly
question before I ask it,
but can you Americans speak
any other language than English?
We both speak a little ltalian.
With an atrocious accent, no doubt.
But that doesn't exactly
kill us in the crib.
Germans don't have a
good ear for ltalian.
So you mumble ltalian and brazen
through it. Is that the plan?
That's about it.
That sounds good.
It sounds like shit. What else
are we going to do? Go home?
No, that sounds good.
If you don't blow it, with that,
I can get you in the building.
Who does what?
Well, I speak the most ltalian,
so I'll be your escort.
Donowitz speaks second most, so
he'll be your Italian cameraman.
Omar, third most. He'll
be Donny's assistant.
I don't speak ltalian.
Like I said, third best. Just
keep your fucking mouth shut.
In fact, why don't you
start practicing right now?
Yes.
Gorlomi?
Gorlomi.
Antonio Margheriti.
Margheriti.
Dominick Decocco.
What's that American expression?
"If the shoe fits, you must wear it."
Fucking shithead.
Faggot fuck. Fuck you!
Bunch of shithead fuck.
Fuck you, too!
Goddamn Nazi farts, sons of
bitches! Get your hands off me.
You fucking bratwurst-smelling...
Goddamn you! Get off!
Hmm.
You Jerry-banging,
Limburg-smelling...
As Stanley said to Livingstone,
Lieutenant Aldo Raine, I presume?
Hans Landa.
You've had a nice long run, Aldo.
Alas, you're now in the hands of the SS.
My hands to be exact.
And they've been waiting
a long time to touch you.
Caught you flinching.
Touch me again, Kraut-burger.
Utivich?
Is that you, Lieutenant?
Yeah.
Do you know what happened to Donny?
Omar?
The woman?
No, I do not.
Tell me, Aldo, if I were
sitting where you're sitting,
would you show me mercy?
Nope.
What is that English
expression about shoes and feet?
"Looks like the shoe is on the other
foot." Yeah, I was just thinking that.
So you're Aldo the Apache.
So you're The Jew Hunter.
I'm a detective.
A damn good detective.
Finding people is my specialty,
so naturally, I worked for
the Nazis finding people.
And, yes, some of them
were Jews. But Jew Hunter?
Just a name that stuck.
Well, you do have to
admit, it is catchy.
Do you control the nicknames
your enemies bestow on you?
Aldo the Apache and the Little Man?
What do you mean the Little Man?
Germans' nickname for you.
The Germans' nickname
for me is the Little Man?
And as if to make my point, I'm a little
surprised how tall you were in real life.
l mean, you're a little fellow,
but not circus-midget little,
as your reputation would suggest.
Where's my men?
Where's Bridget von Hammersmark?
Well, let's just say,
she got what she deserved.
And when you purchase friends
like Bridget von Hammersmark,
you get what you pay for.
Now as far as your paesanos,
Sergeant Donowitz and Private Omar...
How you know our names?
Lieutenant Aldo,
if you don't think I
wouldn't interrogate
every single one of your
swastika-marked survivors,
we simply aren't operating on the
level of mutual respect I assumed.
No, I guess not.
Well, back to the whereabouts
of your two ltalian saboteurs.
As of this moment,
both Omar and Donowitz should be sitting
in the very seats we left them in.
Double-zero 23 and double-zero 24,
if my memory serves.
Explosives still around their
ankles, still ready to explode.
And your mission, some
would call a terrorist plot,
as of this moment, is still a go.
That's a pretty exciting story.
What's next? Eliza on lce?
However,
all I have to do is pick
up this phone right here,
inform the cinema,
and your plan is kaput.
If they're still here, and if they're
still alive, and that's one big if,
there ain't no way you're
going to take them boys
without setting off them bombs.
I have no doubt.
And, yes, some Germans will die.
Yes, it will ruin the evening.
And, yes, Goebbels will be
very, very, very mad at you
for what you've done to his big night.
But you won't get Hitler,
you won't get Goebbels,
you won't get Goring,
and you won't get Bormann.
And you need all four to end the war.
But if I don't pick up
this phone right here,
you may very well get all four.
And if you get all four, you end the war
tonight.
So, gentlemen,
let's discuss the prospect
of ending the war tonight.
So, the way I see it,
since Hitler's death or possible
rescue rests solely on my reaction,
if I do nothing,
it's as if I'm causing his
death even more than yourselves.
Wouldn't you agree?
I guess so.
How about you, Utivich?
I guess so, too.
Gentlemen, l have no intention
of killing Hitler and killing Goebbels
and killing Goring and killing Bormann,
not to mention winning the war
single-handedly for the Allies,
only later to find myself
standing before a Jewish tribunal.
If you want to win the war tonight,
we have to make a deal.
What kind of deal?
The kind you wouldn't
have the authority to make.
However, I'm sure this mission
of yours has a commanding officer.
A general.
I'm betting for...
OSS would be my guess.
That's a bingo!
Is that the way you say
it? "That's a bingo."
You just say, "Bingo."
Bingo! How fun.
But I digress. Where were
we? Yeah! Make a deal.
Over there is a very capable
two-way radio and sitting behind it
is a more than capable
radio operator named Hermann.
Get me someone on the
other end of that radio
with the power of the
pen to authorize my,
let's call it, the terms
of my conditional surrender.
If that tastes better going down.
You know, where I'm from...
Yeah? Where is that exactly?
Maynardville, Tennessee.
I've done my share of bootlegging.
Up there, if you engage in what the
federal government calls illegal activity,
but what we call just a man trying
to make a living for his family
selling moonshine liquor, it
behooves oneself to keep his wits.
Long story short, we hear
a story too good to be true,
it ain't.
Sitting in your chair, l would
probably say the same thing,
and 999.999 times out of a
million, you would be correct.
But in the pages of history,
every once in a while,
fate reaches out and extends its hand.
What shall the history books read?
I implore you. We
must destroy that tower.
Sarge, that tower...
The tower stands!
Psst! Psst!
So when the military
history of this night is written,
it will be recorded that I
was part of Operation Kino
from the very beginning
as a double agent.
Anything I've done in
my guise as an SS Colonel
was sanctioned by the
OSS as a necessary evil
to establish my cover with the Germans.
And it was my placement of
Lieutenant Raine's dynamite
in Hitler and Goebbels' opera
box that assured their demise.
By the way, that last
part is actually true.
I want my full military pension
and benefits under my proper rank.
I want to receive the
Congressional Medal of Honor
for my invaluable assistance in
the toppling of the Third Reich.
In fact, I want all the
members of Operation Kino
to receive the
Congressional Medal of Honor.
Full citizenship for myself.
Well, that goes without saying.
And I would like the
United States of America
to purchase property for
me on Nantucket lsland
as a reward for all the
countless lives I've saved
by bringing the tyranny of
the National Socialist Party
to a swifter-than-imagined end.
Do you have all that, sir?
l look forward to seeing you
face to face as well, sir.
Lieutenant Raine? Right here.
Yes, sir.
Colonel Landa will put you and
Private Utivich in a truck as prisoners.
Then he and his radio operator will
get in the truck and drive to our lines.
Upon crossing our lines, Colonel Landa
and his man will surrender to you.
You will then take over
driving of the truck
and bring them straight to me for
debriefing. ls that clear, Lieutenant?
Yes, sir.
Over and out.
When I kill that guy, you got
30 feet to get to that guard.
Can you do it? I have to.
Champagne?
Who wants to send a message to Germany?
I have a message for Germany.
That you are all going to die.
And I want you to look deep into the
face of the Jew who's going to do it!
Marcel, burn it down.
Oui, Shosanna.
My name is Shosanna Dreyfus,
and this is the face
of Jewish vengeance.
Hermann, uncuff them.
I'm officially surrendering myself
over to you, Lieutenant Raine.
We're your prisoners.
How about my knife?
Thank you very much, Colonel.
Utivich, cuff the Colonel's
hands behind his back.
ls that really necessary?
I'm a slave to appearances.
Scalp Hermann.
Are you mad?
What have you done?
I made a deal with your
general for that man's life!
Yeah, they made that deal. But they
don't give a fuck about him. They need you.
You'll be shot for this!
Nah, I don't think so. More like
chewed out. I've been chewed out before.
You know, Utivich and myself heard
that deal you made with the brass.
End the war tonight?
I'd make that deal.
How about you, Utivich?
You make that deal?
I'd make that deal.
I don't blame you. Damn good deal.
And that pretty little nest
you feathered for yourself.
Well, if you're willing to
barbecue the whole High Command,
l suppose that's worth
certain considerations.
But I do have one question.
When you get to your little
place on Nantucket lsland,
l imagine you are going to take off that
handsome-looking SS uniform of yours.
Ain't you?
That's what I thought.
Now, that I can't abide.
How about you, Utivich,
can you abide it?
Not one damn bit, sir.
l mean, if I had my way,
you'd wear that goddamn uniform for
the rest of your pecker-sucking life.
But I'm aware that ain't practical.
I mean, at some point, you're
going to have to take it off.
So,
I'm going to give you a little
something you can't take off.
You know something, Utivich?
I think this just
might be my masterpiece.