Do you find me sadistic?
You know, Kiddo,
I'd like to believe
you're aware enough, even now,
to know that there's
nothing sadistic
in my actions.
At this moment
this is me
at my most masochistic.
Bill.. it's your ba..
Looked dead, didn't I?
Well, I wasn't.
But it wasn't from lack of
trying, I can tell you that.
Actually, Bill's last bullet
put me in a coma -
a coma I was to lie in
for four years.
When I woke up, I went on
what the movie advertisements
refer to as
"a roaring rampage
of revenge."
I roared and I rampaged,
and I got bloody satisfaction.
I've killed a hell of a lot of
people to get to this point,
but I have only one more.
The last one.
The one I'm driving to
right now.
The only one left.
And when I arrive
at my destination,
I am gonna kill Bill.
Kill Bill Vol 2
Blu-ray
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Now, the incident
that happened
at the Two Pines Wedding Chapel
that put this whole gory
story into motion
has since become legend.
"Massacre at Two Pines."
That's what the newspapers
called it.
The local TV news called it
"The El Paso, Texas,
Wedding Chapel Massacre."
How it happened,
who was there,
how many got killed
and who killed them
changes depending on
who's telling the story.
In actual fact,
the massacre didn't happen
during a wedding at all.
It was a wedding rehearsal.
Now, when we come
to the part where I say,
"You may kiss the bride,"
you may kiss the bride,
but don't stick your tongue
in her mouth.
This might be funny
to your friends,
but it would be embarrassing
to your parents.
We'll try to restrain
ourselves, Reverend.
Y'all got a song?
How 'bout "Love Me Tender"?
I can play that.
Sure.
Yeah.
"Love Me Tender" 'd be great.
Rufus - he's the man.
Rufus, who was that
that you used to play for?
Rufus Thomas.
I was a Drell.
I was a Drifter.
I was a Coaster.
I was part of the Gang.
I was a Bar-Kay.
If they come through Texas,
I played with 'em.
Rufus - he's the man.
Have I forgotten anything?
Um..
Oh, yes. You forgot, uh,
the seating arrangements.
Thank you, Mother.
Yes.
Now, the way we
normally do this,
we have the bride's side,
and then we have
the groom's side.
But since the bride
ain't got nobody comin',
and the groom's got
far too many people comin'..
Well, yeah, they're comin'
all the way from Oklahoma.
Right.. Well, I don't
see no problem with..
the groom's side sharing
the bride's side.
Do you, Mother?
I don't have
a problem with that.
But, uh..
Honey, you know, it would be
good if you had somebody come.
You know, as a sign
of good faith?
Well, I don't have anybody,
except for Tommy
and my friends.
You have no family?
Well, I'm workin'
on changing that.
Mrs. Harmony,
we're all the family
this little angel's
ever gonna need.
I'm not feeling very well,
and this bitch is starting
to piss me off.
So while y'all blather on,
I'm gonna go outside
and get some air.
OK.
Um, uh, Reverend,
sorry, uh..
She's gonna go out
and get some air.
Yeah. Given her delicate
condition.
She just needs a few minutes
to get it together.
She'll be OK.
Right.
Hello, Kiddo.
How did you find me?
I'm the man.
What are you doin' here?
What am I doin'?
Well,
a moment ago
I was playing my flute.
At this moment
I'm lookin' at the most
beautiful bride
these old eyes have ever seen.
Why are you here?
Last look.
Are you gonna be nice?
I've never been nice
my whole life.
But I'll do my best
to be sweet.
Hmm.
I always told you,
your sweet side
is your best side.
I guess that's why you're
the only one who's ever seen it.
I see you got a bun
in the oven.
Hmm. I'm knocked up.
Jeez, Louise.
That young man of yours
sure doesn't believe
in wasting time, does he?
Have you seen Tommy?
Big guy in the tux?
Yes.
Then I saw him.
I like his hair.
You promised you'd be nice.
No, I said I'd do my best.
That's hardly a promise.
But you're right.
What does your young man do
for a living?
He owns a used-record store
here in El Paso.
Ah. Music lover, eh?
He's fond of music.
Aren't we all?
And what are you doing
for a J-O-B these days?
I work in the record store.
Aso.
It all suddenly seems so clear.
Do you like it?
Yeah. I like it
a lot, smartass.
I get to listen to music all
day, talk about music all day.
It's really cool.
It's gonna be a great
environment
for my little girl
to grow up in.
As opposed to jetting
around the world,
killing human beings
and being paid
vast sums of money?
Precisely.
Well, my old friend,
to each his own.
However,
all cockblockery aside,
I am looking forward
to meeting your young man.
I happen to be, more or less,
particular whom my gal marries.
You want to come
to the wedding?
Only if I can sit
on the bride's side.
You'll find it a bit lonely
on my side.
Your side always
was a bit lonely.
But I wouldn't sit
anywhere else.
You know,
I had the loveliest dream
about you..
Oh, here's Tommy!
Call me Arlene.
You must be Tommy!
Uh-huh.
Arlene's told me
so much about you.
Honey, you OK?
Oh, I'm fine.
Tommy, I'd like you
to meet my father.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, this is great!
I'm so glad to meet you,
sir.. oh, Dad.
The name's Bill.
Well, it's great
to meet you.. Bill.
Arlene told me
you couldn't make it.
Surprise.
That's my pop for ya.
Always full of surprises.
Well,
in the surprise department,
the apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
When did you get in?
Just now.
Did you come straight
from Australia?
Of course.
Daddy, I told Tommy that you
were in Perth mining for silver,
and no one could reach you.
Lucky for us all,
that's not the case.
So.. What's this all about?
I've heard of
wedding rehearsals,
but I don't believe
I've ever heard of
a wedding dress rehearsal
before.
We thought, "Why pay
so much money for a dress"
you're only gonna wear once?"
Especially when Arlene looks
so goddamn beautiful in it.
So I think we're gonna try
to get all the mileage
we can out of it.
Isn't it supposed to be
bad luck for the groom
to see the bride
in her wedding dress
before the ceremony?
Well..
I guess I just believe
in living dangerously.
I know just what you mean.
Son.
Some of us have places to be.
Sure do.
Look, we gotta go through this
one more time,
so why don't you have a s..
Oh, my God.
What am I thinking?
You should give her away!
Tommy, that's not exactly
Daddy's cup of tea.
I think Father would
be much more comfortable
sitting with the rest
of the guests.
Hmm. Really?
That's asking a lot.
Oh. OK. Well, forget it.
But how about we go
out to dinner tonight
to celebrate?
Only on the condition
that I pay for everything.
Deal. We got to do this now.
Can I watch?
Absolutely. Have a seat.
Which is the bride's side?
Right over here.
Mother, here we go!
Now, son, about them vows..
Bill.. I just want..
You don't owe me a damn thing.
If he's the man you want,
then go stand by him.
Do I look pretty?
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
What the hell?
No! Bill!
You tellin' me she cut her way
through 88 bodyguards
'fore she got to O-Ren?
Nah, there wasn't
really 88 of 'em.
They just call themselves
"The Crazy 88."
How come?
I don't know.
I guess they thought
it sounded cool.
Anyhow, they all fell
under her Hanzo sword.
She got a Hanzo sword?
He made one for her.
Didn't he swear a blood oath
to never make another sword?
It would appear
he has broken it.
Them Japs sure know how
to hold a grudge, don't they?
Or maybe.. you just tend
to bring that out in people.
I know this is a ridiculous
question before I ask it,
but you haven't, by any chance,
kept up with your.. swordplay?
I, um..
I pawned that
years ago.
You hocked a Hattori Hanzo
sword?
Yep.
It was priceless.
Well, not in El Paso, it ain't.
In El Paso,
I got me $250 for it.
I'm a bouncer
in a titty bar, Bill.
If she wants to fight with me,
all she's gotta do is
come down to the club
and start some shit,
and we'll be in a fight.
I know we haven't spoken
in some time,
and the last time we spoke
wasn't the most pleasant,
but you've got to get over
being mad at me
and start becoming
afraid of
because she is coming,
and she's coming to kill you.
And, unless you accept
my assistance,
I have no doubt
she will succeed.
I don't dodge guilt
and I don't jew out of
paying my comeuppance.
Can't we just..
forget the past?
That woman
deserves her revenge.
And we deserve to die.
But, then again,
so does she.
So I guess
we'll just see.
Won't we?
Late again.
Budd, can't you tell time?
There ain't nobody in here, man.
Is that Budd?
Yeah.
Tell him to get
his fucking ass back here!
OK.
Budd, Larry'd like a word
with ya.
Take a hit. Be somebody, baby.
You looking for me?
I don't know what car wash
you worked before you came here
that let you stroll in
20 minutes late,
but it wasn't owned by me
and I own a fuckin' car wash.
Do you want me to leave?
No, I don't want you
to leave.
I want you to sit and wait.
Larry,
there ain't nobody
out there, so..
"There's nobody
out there, Larry."
What's your point?
That you're not needed here?
My point is I'm the bouncer,
and there ain't nobody
out there to bounce.
You saying that the reason
that you're not doing the job
that I'm paying you to do
is that you don't
have a job to do?
No..
Is that what you're saying?
What are you trying
to convince me of, exactly?
That you're as useless
as an asshole right here?
Well, guess what, buddy.
I think you just fucking
convinced me.
Let's go to the calendar.
It's calendar time.
Calendar time for Buddy.
OK. You working tomorrow?
Yeah.
Mm. No, you're n..
You don't even know
what fucking day you work.
Here. You're not working
tomorrow.
You're working Wednesday.
Here you are. There you go.
Workin' Thursday?
Yeah.
I don't think so. Friday?
I d.. There's your name.
If you say so.
There used to be
your name. OK?
Saturday.
There used to be your name.
Oh.
Uh, Monday..
Here, how about that?
Fuckin' with your cash
is the only thing
you kids seem to understand. OK?
Now, I want you to go home
till I call you.
Till I call you.
Before you leave,
talk to Rocket.
She's got a job for you to do.
And..
the hat.
That fuckin' hat.
That fucking hat.
How many times have I told you,
don't wear that fucking hat
here? How many?
Customers wear hats.
Well, I'm not the boss
of the customers.
I'm the boss of you.
And I'm telling you
that I want you
to keep that shit-kicker hat
at home.
Yeah, Budd, honey, uh,
the toilet is at it again.
There's shitty water
all over the floor.
OK.. Rocket.
I'll clean it up.
Mm-hmm.
Now,
that gentled you down some,
didn't it?
Yep.
Ain't nobody a badass
with a double dose of rock salt
dug deep in her tits.
Not havin'.. tits
as fine
or as big as yours,
I can't even imagine
how bad that shit must sting.
Yet..
I don't want to, neither.
I win.
Bill.
Wrong brother, ya hateful bitch.
Budd.
Bingo.
And to what do I owe
this dubious pleasure?
I just caught me the cowgirl
that ain't never been caught.
Did you kill her?
Well, not yet, I ain't.
I shot her full of rock salt.
She's so gentle right now,
I could perform her
coup de grâce with a rock.
Anywho..
Guess what I'm holdin'
in my hand right now.
What?
A brand-spankin'-new
Hattori Hanzo sword.
And I'm here to tell ya, Elle,
that's what I call sharp.
How much?
Oh, that's hard to say,
bein' that it's..
priceless an' all.
What's the terms?
You get your bony ass down here
first thing in the morning
with a million dollars
in folding cash,
and I'll give you the greatest
sword ever made by a man.
Now, how do you like
the sound of that?
Sounds like we got a deal.
One condition.
What?
She must suffer
to her last breath.
Well..
That, Elle darlin',
I can pretty much
damn well guarantee.
Then I'll see you
in the mornin', millionaire.
All right.
Wakey-wakey. Eggs and bakey.
Agh!
I'm done!
Get me outta this hole!
Good.
Whew.
Whoa, look at those eyes.
This bitch is furious.
What did I tell ya?
Is she the cutest little
blond pussy you ever saw?
Or.. is she the cutest little
I seen better.
You got anything to say?
White women call this
"the silent treatment."
And we let 'em think
we don't like it.
You grab the feet,
I'll get the head.
Hey. Hey. Hey!
Wiggle worm, you see this?
You see it, don't ya?
That's a can of Mace.
Mm-hmm. No.
You're goin' underneath
the ground tonight.
And.. that's all
there is to it.
I wanna bury ya.
I was gonna bury ya..
with this.
But if you're gonna act
like a horse's ass,
I'm gonna spray
this whole goddamn can
right in your eyeballs!
I'll burn 'em right
outta your fuckin' head.
Then you're gonna be blind
and burnin'
and buried alive.
Now, what's it gonna be, sister?
That's a wise decision.
This is for breakin'
my brother's heart.
Once upon a time
in China,
some believe around the year
one, double aught, three,
head priest of
the White Lotus Clan, Pai Mei,
was walking down a road
contemplating whatever it is
that a man of Pai Mei's
infinite powers
would contemplate -
which is another way
of saying "Who knows?" -
when a Shaolin monk
appeared on the road,
traveling in the opposite
direction.
As the monk and the priest
crossed paths,
Pai Mei,
in a practically unfathomable
display of generosity,
gave the monk
the slightest of nods.
The nod
was not returned.
Now, was it the intention
of the Shaolin monk
to insult Pai Mei?
Or did he just fail to see
the generous social gesture?
The motives of the monk
remain unknown.
What is known
were the consequences.
The next morning,
Pai Mei appeared
at the Shaolin temple
and demanded
of the temple's head abbot
that he offer Pai Mei his neck
to repay the insult.
The abbot, at first,
tried to console Pai Mei,
only to find Pai Mei was
inconsolable.
So began
the Massacre
of the Shaolin Temple
and all sixty
of the monks inside,
at the fists of the White Lotus.
And so began the legend
of Pai Mei's Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique.
And what, pray tell,
is the Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique?
Quite simply, the deadliest blow
in all of martial arts.
He hits you with his fingertips
at five different pressure
points on your body,
and then lets you walk away.
But once you've taken five steps
your heart explodes
inside your body
and you fall to the floor, dead.
Did he teach you that?
No.
He teaches no one
the Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique.
Now,
one of the things I've always
liked about you, Kiddo,
is you appear wise
beyond your years.
So, allow me to impart
a word to the wise.
Whatever..
Whatever Pai Mei says, obey.
If you flash him, even for
an instant, a defiant eye,
he'll pluck it out.
And if you throw
any American sass his way,
he'll snap your back and your
neck like they were twigs.
And that will be
the story of you.
He'll accept you as his student.
What happened to you?
Nothin'.
Get in a fight?
Friendly contest.
Why did he accept me?
Because he's a very,
very, very old man.
And, like all rotten bastards,
when they become old,
they get lonely.
Which has no effect
on their dispositions,
but it does teach them
the value of company.
Whew. Oh.
Just seein' those
steps again makes me ache.
You're gonna have a lot of fun
carrying buckets of water
up and down that fucker.
When will I see you again?
That's the title of my favorite
soul song of the 70s.
What?
Nothin'.
When he tells me you're done.
When do you think
that might be?
That, my dearest,
depends entirely on you.
Now remember,
no sarcasm, no back talk.
At least not
for the first year or so.
You're gonna have to
let him warm up to you.
He hates Caucasians,
despises Americans,
and has nothing
but contempt for women.
So in your case..
it might take a little while.
Adiós.
A little.
I am proficient
in Tiger-Crane Style,
and I am more than proficient
in the exquisite art
of the Samurai sword.
Argh!
No, please don't!
Aaargh!
Yes!
Come on, you bitch.
OK, Pai Mei.
Here I come.
May I have a glass
of water, please?
So that's a Texas funeral?
Yep.
I have to give it to ya, Budd.
That's a pretty
fucked-up way to die.
What's the name on the grave
she's buried under?
Paula
Schultz.
Can I look at the sword?
That's my money right there
in that red bag, isn't it?
It sure is.
Well, then,
it's your sword now.
What's that you said?
So this is
a Hattori Hanzo sword.
That's a Hanzo sword,
all right.
Bill tells me you once had
one of these of your own.
Yeah, once.
Yeah? How does this one
compare to that?
If you're gonna compare
a Hanzo sword,
you compare it to every
other sword ever made -
wasn't made - by Hattori Hanzo.
Here you go.
Wrap your lips around that.
So,
which "R" are you filled with?
What?
They say
the number-one killer
of old people
is retirement.
People got a job to do,
they tend to live a little bit
longer so they can do it.
I've always figured that
warriors and their enemies
share the same relationship.
So now that you're
not gonna have to
face your enemy no more
on the battlefield,
which "R" ya filled with?
Relief?
Or regret?
A little bit of both.
Horseshit.
I'm sure you do feel
a little bit of both.
But I know damn well
that you feel one
more than you feel the other.
And the question was,
which one is it?
Regret.
You know, you gotta
hand it to the old girl.
I never saw anybody buffalo Bill
the way she buffaloed Bill.
Bill thought
she was so damn smart.
And I tried to tell him
she was just smart for a blonde.
Thanks a bunch.
All right.
Argh! Argh!
Mmm.
I'm sorry, Budd.
That was rude of me,
wasn't it?
Budd, I'd like to introduce
my friend, the black mamba.
Black mamba, this is Budd.
You know, before I picked
that little fella up,
I looked him up on the Internet.
Fascinating creature,
the black mamba.
Listen to this.
"In Africa, the saying goes"
'In the bush,
an elephant can kill you,
a leopard can kill you,
and a black mamba
can kill you.
But only with the mamba,
and this has been
true in Africa
since the dawn of time,
"is death sure.'"
"Hence its handle,
'Death Incarnate.'"
Pretty cool, huh?
"Its neurotoxic venom is one of
nature's most effective poisons,
acting on the nervous system,
causing paralysis."
"The venom of a black mamba
can kill a human being
in four hours
if, say, bitten on the ankle
or the thumb."
"However, a bite
to the face or torso
can bring death from paralysis
within 20 minutes."
Now, you should listen to this,
'cause this concerns you.
"The amount of venom that can
be delivered from a single bite
can be gargantuan."
You know, I've always liked
that word "gargantuan."
I so rarely have an opportunity
to use it in a sentence.
"If not treated quickly
with antivenom,
ten to 15 milligrams
can be fatal to human beings."
"However, the black mamba
can deliver"
as much as 100 to 400
milligrams of venom
"from a single bite."
Now,
in these last agonizing
minutes of life you have left,
let me answer that question
you asked earlier
more thoroughly.
Right at this moment
the biggest "R" I feel
is regret.
Regret that maybe
the greatest warrior
I have ever met
met her end at the hands
of a bushwhackin', scrub,
alky piece of shit like you.
That woman deserved better.
Bill.
I have some tragic news.
Your brother's dead.
I am so sorry, baby.
She put a black mamba
in his camper.
I got her, sweetie. She's dead.
Let me put it this way,
you ever start feeling
sentimental,
go to Barstow, California.
When you get here,
walk into a florist
and buy a bunch of flowers.
Then you take those flowers
to Huntington Cemetery
on Fuller and Guadalupe,
look for the headstone
marked "Paula Schultz,"
and lay them on the grave.
'Cause you will be standing
at the final resting place
of Beatrix Kiddo.
Marty Kitrosser?
Here.
Melanie Harrhouse?
Beatrix Kiddo?
Here.
Look.. I can be there
in about four hours.
Do you want me to come over?
No, no, no, no.
You need me, baby, I'm there.
OK. I'm leaving now.
You go smoke some pot
or somethin'.
I'll be there soon.
Ugh.
Gross.
Yaagh!
Agh!
Hi-ya!
"To my brother, Budd.
The only man I ever loved.
Bill."
What's that?
Budd's Hanzo sword.
He said he pawned it.
Guess that makes him
a liar now, don't it?
Elle?
Bea.
Somethin' I've always
been curious about.
Just between us girls,
what did you say to Pai Mei
to make him snatch out your eye?
Argh! Ow! Ow!
I called him a miserable
old fool.
Ooh.
Bad idea.
Know what I did?
I killed that miserable
old fool.
How do you
like the fish head,
you miserable old fool?
I poisoned his fish heads.
And I told him "To me,
the word of an old fool like you"
is worth less than nothing."
That's right.
I killed your master.
And now I'm gonna kill you, too.
With your own sword, no less.
Which, in the very immediate
future, will become my sword.
Bitch.
You don't have a future.
Fucking bitch!
I'll kill you!
You're fuckin' dead!
You bitch! You bitch!
I'll fucking kill you,
you bitch!
Oh, I'll get you!
I'm gonna..
Where are you?
Lemme fuckin' at you!
I'm coming, you fucking bitch!
You're fucking dead!
You're dead!
Oh.. shit!
Like most men
who never knew their father,
Bill collected father figures.
The first was Esteban Vihaio.
Esteban was a pimp
and a friend of Bill's mother.
He ran a brothel in Acuna,
Mexico, for over 50 years.
His army, the Acuna Boys,
made up of the fatherless
offspring of his whores,
ran Acuna.
He ran the Acuna Boys.
Now, at the age of 80,
it would be this retired
gentleman of leisure
who could point me
in Bill's direction.
Señor Esteban Vihaio?
Yes.
May I join you?
Only on the condition
that you call me Esteban.
May I join you, Esteban?
Please.
¿Americana?
Yes.
I speak a little Spanish,
if you prefer.
No, no, no, no.
I prefer English.
I haven't spoken it in a while,
but I would relish
the opportunity to converse
with such a pretty
companion as yourself.
It's my pleasure to be
in the company
of such a fine gentleman
as yourself.
I must warn you, young lady,
I am susceptible to flattery.
How may I be of service to you?
Where's Bill?
Ahh.
You must be Beatrix.
I can see the attraction.
I remember when Bill
was only five years old,
I took him to the movies.
It was a movie
starring Lana Turner.
The Postman Always Ring Twice,
with John Garfield.
And whenever she would
appear on the screen,
Bill would begin compulsively
to suck his thumb
to an obscene amount.
And I knew from this very moment
this boy was a fool for blondes.
Mmm.
You know,
being a fool for a woman
such as yourself
is always the right thing to do.
If we had met
when I was back in business,
you would have been
my number-one lady.
Well, I'm flattered.
You goddamn well better be.
This.. I heard you
were driving a truck.
My Pussy Wagon died on me.
The Pussy died. Hmm.
Bill shot you in the head, no?
Yes.
Hmm.
I would have been much nicer.
I would have just cut your face.
You must forgive me.
Please.. you have
a drink with me.
Clara!
Coming.
Dos añejo.
Gracias.
What were we talking about?
Bill.
Where's Bill?
Where's Bill.
Yeah. Hmm.
Bill is at the Villa Quatro,
on the road to Salina.
I will draw you a map.
Bill is like a son to me.
Do you know why I help you?
No.
Because he would want me to.
Now, that I don't believe.
Ahh.
How else is he ever
going to see you again?
Freeze, Mommy.
Bang, bang! Oh!
Oh! She got us, B.B.
Mommy got us.
Oh, I'm dying.
I'm dying.
Fall down, sweetheart.
Mommy shot us.
But little did
Quickdraw Kiddo know
that little B.B.
was only playing possum,
due to the fact that
she was impervious to bullets.
I am pervious
to bullets, Mommy.
Hey, get back down there.
You're playing possum.
So, as the smirking killer
advanced on what she thought
was a bullet-ridden corpse,
that's when little B.B. fired.
Bang, bang!
You're dead, Mommy. So die.
Oh!
B.B.
Oh! B.B..
I should've known.
You are.. the best.
Oh, Mommy. Don't die.
I was just playing.
I know.
I told her that you were asleep,
but that one day you'd wake up
and come back to her.
And she asked me, "If Mommy's
been asleep since I was born",
then how will she know
what I look like?"
To which I replied, "Because
Mommy's been dreaming of you."
That's what I said.
Did you dream of me?
I dreamed of you.
Every single night, baby.
Every single night.
I waited a long time
for you to wake up, Mommy.
Now, let me look at you.
Oh.
My, my, my, what a pretty
little girl you are.
You're pretty too, Mommy.
Tell Mommy what you said
when I showed you her picture.
Mm-mm.
Come on, shy girl.
Come on.
You know what you said.
Come on. Tell Mommy.
It'll make her feel good.
Come on.
Mm-mm.
Yeah. Come on.
I said.. I said
"You're the most
beautifulest woman
I ever saw
in the whole wide world."
That's the truth.
That's what she said.
B.B., don't you think Mommy
has the prettiest hair
in the whole wide world?
Yes, I do.
Matter of fact,
it's better than pretty.
What's better than pretty?
Mmm.. Gorgeous.
Very good. Gorgeous.
Mommy is gorgeous.
Hmm. You know, sweetie,
Mommy's kinda mad at Daddy.
Why, Daddy?
Were you being a bad daddy?
I'm afraid I was.
I was a real bad daddy.
Our little girl learned about
life and death the other day.
Wanna tell Mommy about
what happened to Emilio?
I killed him.
Emilio was her goldfish.
Emilio was my goldfiss.
She came running into my room,
holding the fish in her hand
and crying,
"Daddy! Daddy! Emilio's dead."
And I said,
"Really? That's so sad."
"How did he die?"
And what did you say?
I stepped on him.
Actually, young lady, the words
you so strategically used were
"I accidentally stepped on him."
To which I queried,
"And just how did
your foot accidentally
find its way
into Emilio's fishbowl?"
And she said, "No, no, no."
Emilio was on the carpet
when I stepped on him."
Mmm. The plot thickens.
"And just how did Emilio
get on the carpet?"
And, Mommy, you would've
been so proud of her.
She didn't lie.
She said she took Emilio
out of his bowl
and put him on the carpet.
And what was Emilio
doing on the carpet?
Flapping.
And then you stomped on him.
Uh-huh.
And when you lifted up
your foot,
what was Emilio doing then?
Nothing.
He stopped flapping,
didn't he?
She told me later
that the second
she lifted up her foot
and saw Emilio not flapping,
she knew what she had done.
Is that not the perfect
visual image of life and death?
A fish flapping on the carpet,
and a fish not flapping
on the carpet.
So powerful,
even a four-year-old
with no concept of life or death
knew what it meant.
You loved Emilio,
didn't you?
Uh-huh.
Well, I love Mommy, too.
But I did to Mommy
what you did to Emilio.
You stomped on Mommy?
Worse.
I shot Mommy.
Not pretend shooting
like we were just doing.
I shot her for real.
Why? Did you want to see
what would happen?
No, I knew what would happen
to Mommy if I shot her.
What I didn't know was,
when I shot Mommy,
what would happen to me.
What happened?
I was very sad.
And that's when I learned
some things, once you do,
they can never be undone.
What happened to Mommy?
Why don't you ask Mommy?
You OK, Mommy? Did it hurt?
No, sweetie.
Doesn't hurt anymore.
Did it make you sick?
No. It made me sleep.
That's why I haven't been
with you, B.B.
I've been asleep.
But you're awake now, Mommy.
Right?
I'm wide awake, pretty girl.
B.B., would you like Mommy
to watch a video with you
before sleepy time?
Uh-huh.
Mommy, do you wanna
watch a video with me
before sleepy time?
Oh, yeah! I would love to.
Which one do you
wanna watch?
Shogun Assassin.
No, B.B. Shogun Assassin
is too long.
Mm-mm.
No, it's not.
Well, then,
I'll leave you ladies to it.
When I was little,
my father was famous.
He was the greatest samurai
in the empire.
And he was the shogun's
decapitator.
He cut off the heads
of 131 lords.
My father would
come home to Mother,
and when he would see her
he would forget
about the killings.
He wasn't scared of the shogun,
but the shogun
was scared of him.
Maybe that was the problem.
One night, the shogun sent..
I was just admiring your sword.
Quite a piece of work.
Speaking of which,
how is Hanzo-san?
He's good.
Has his sushi
gotten any better?
You know, I couldn't believe it.
You got him to make you a sword.
It was easy.
I just dropped your name, Bill.
That'd do it.
I suppose the idea is
we cross Hanzo swords.
Am I right?
Well, it just so happens
this hacienda has
its own private beach.
And that private beach
just so happens
to look particularly beautiful
bathed in moonlight.
And there just so happens
to be a full moon out tonight.
So, sword fighter,
if you want a sword fight,
that's where I suggest.
But if you wanna be
old school about it
- and you know
I'm all about old school -
then we could wait until dawn
and slice each other up
at sunrise
like a couple
of real-life, honest..
Now, if you don't settle down,
I'm gonna have to put one
in your kneecap.
And I hear tell that's
a very painful place
to get shot in.
I'm just fuckin' with you.
Now, when it comes to you
and us
I have a few
unanswered questions.
So, before this tale
of bloody revenge
reaches its climax,
I'm gonna ask you
some questions,
and I want you
to tell me the truth.
However, therein lies a dilemma.
Because when it comes
to the subject of me,
I believe you are
truly and utterly
incapable of telling the truth.
Especially to me.
And least of all, to yourself.
And when it comes
to the subject of me,
I am truly and utterly
incapable of believing
anything you say.
How do you suppose
we solve this dilemma?
Well, it just so happens,
I have a solution.
Agh!
Gotcha!
God damn!
What the fuck did you
just shoot me with?
My greatest invention.
Or at least my favorite.
Don't touch it,
or I'll stick another one
right in your cheek.
What lies within that dart,
just begging to course
its way through your veins
is an incredibly potent
and quite infallible
truth serum.
I call it
"The Undisputed Truth."
Twice as strong
as sodium pentothal,
with no druggie aftereffects.
Except for a slight wave
of euphoria. You feel it?
Euphoria?
Yeah.
No.
Too bad.
As you know,
I'm quite keen on comic books.
Especially the ones
about superheroes.
I find the whole mythology
surrounding superheroes
fascinating.
Take my favorite superhero,
Superman.
Not a great comic book.
Not particularly well drawn.
Mmm.
But the mythology..
The mythology is not only
great, it's unique.
How long does this shit take
to go into effect?
About two minutes.
Just long enough for me
to finish my point.
Now, a staple of
the superhero mythology is,
there's the superhero
and there's the alter ego.
Batman is actually Bruce Wayne,
Spider-Man is actually
Peter Parker.
When that character
wakes up in the morning,
he's Peter Parker.
He has to put on a costume
to become Spider-Man.
And it is in that characteristic
Superman stands alone.
Superman didn't become Superman.
Superman was born Superman.
When Superman wakes up
in the morning, he's Superman.
His alter ego is Clark Kent.
His outfit with the big red "S,"
that's the blanket
he was wrapped in as a baby
when the Kents found him.
Those are his clothes.
What Kent wears - the glasses,
the business suit -
that's the costume.
That's the costume Superman
wears to blend in with us.
Clark Kent is how Superman
views us.
And what are the characteristics
of Clark Kent?
He's weak,
he's unsure of himself,
he's a coward.
Clark Kent is
Superman's critique
on the whole human race.
Sorta like Beatrix Kiddo
and Mrs. Tommy Plympton.
Aso.
The point emerges.
You would've worn the costume
of Arlene Plympton.
But you were born Beatrix Kiddo.
And every morning
when you woke up,
you'd still be Beatrix Kiddo.
Oh, you can take
the needle out.
Are you calling me a superhero?
I'm calling you a killer.
A natural-born killer.
You always have been,
and you always will be.
Moving to El Paso,
working in
a used-record store,
goin' to the movies with Tommy,
clipping coupons.
That's you
trying to disguise yourself
as a worker bee.
That's you tryin'
to blend in with the hive.
But you're not a worker bee.
You're a renegade killer bee.
And no matter how much beer
you drank or barbecue you ate
or how fat your ass got,
nothing in the world
would ever change that.
First question:
did you really think your life
in El Paso was gonna work?
No!
But I would've had B.B.!
Don't get me wrong.
I think you would have been
a wonderful mother.
But you are a killer.
All those people you killed
to get to me
felt damn good, didn't they?
Yes.
Every single one of them?
That was the warmup round.
Now comes the $64,000 question.
Why did you run away from me
with my baby?
Do you remember the last
assignment you sent me on?
Of course.
Lisa Wong.
The morning I left, I was sick.
On the plane, I threw up.
So I started thinking
maybe I was pregnant.
"Easy to use.
Remove cap and urinate
on the absorbent end
for five seconds."
"Accurate results
in only 90 seconds."
"You can read the results
as soon as the line appears
in the window."
Fuck.
What I didn't know
was that somewhere
on my journey
I had been spotted.
With me in L.A.,
it didn't take Lisa Wong long
to send an assassin of her own.
Hello,
can I help you?
Hello, I'm Karen Kim.
I'm the hospitality manager
of the hotel.
I have a welcome gift
from the management.
Oh, that's nice. Um..
Can you just leave it
by the door?
You pretty good
with that shotgun?
Not that I have to be
at this range,
but I'm a fuckin' surgeon
with this shotgun.
Well, guess what, bitch.
I'm better than Annie Oakley,
and I got you
right in my sight.
I could blow
your fuckin' head off.
Not before I put one
right between your eyes,
so let's talk.
Karen..
I just found out
right now
not a moment before you blew
a hole through the door
that I'm pregnant.
What is this?
On the floor by the door
is a strip that says
I'm pregnant.
Bullshit.
Any other time
you'd be 100 percent right.
This time
you're 100 percent wrong.
I'm the deadliest woman
in the world.
But right now
I'm just scared shitless
for my baby.
Please.
Just look at the strip.
Please!
Stay where you are
and don't move.
I don't know what
this fuckin' shit means.
The box with the directions -
it's right there.
"Easy to use."
"Remove the cap and urinate
on the absorbent end."
Blue means pregnant.
I'll read it myself,
thank you.
Oh, OK. Say I were
to believe you. What then?
Just go home.
I'll do the same.
Congratulations.
Before that strip turned blue
I was a woman. I was your woman.
I was a killer
who killed for you.
Before that strip turned blue,
I would've jumped a motorcycle
onto a speeding train.
For you.
But once that strip turned blue
I could no longer
do any of those things.
Not anymore.
Because I was gonna be a mother.
Can you understand that?
Yes.
But why didn't you tell me then,
instead of now?
Once you knew, you'd claim her.
And I didn't want that.
Not your decision to make.
Yes.
But it's the right decision,
and I made it for my daughter.
She deserved to be born
with a clean slate.
But with you
she would've been born
into a world she shouldn't have.
I had to choose.
I chose her.
You know, five years ago,
if I had to make a list
of impossible things
that could never happen,
you performing
a coup de grâce on me
by bustin' a cap in my crown
would've been right
at the top of the list.
I'd have been wrong,
wouldn't I?
I'm sorry.
Was that a question?
Of impossible things
that could never happen,
yes, in this instance,
you would've been wrong.
Well?
When you never came back,
I naturally assumed Lisa Wong,
or somebody else,
had killed you.
Oh! And for the record,
letting somebody think
somebody they love is dead
when they're not
is quite cruel.
I mourned you for three months.
And in the third month
of mourning you
I tracked you down.
I wasn't tryin'
to track you down.
I was tryin' to track down
the fucking assholes
I thought killed you.
So I find you.
And what do I find?
Not only are you not dead,
you're getting married
to some fucking jerk.
And you're pregnant.
I.. overreacted.
You overreacted?
Is that your explanation?
I didn't say I was
gonna explain myself.
I said I was gonna
tell you the truth.
But if that's too cryptic,
let's get literal.
I'm a killer.
I'm a murdering bastard.
You know that.
And there are consequences
to breaking the heart
of a murdering bastard.
You experienced some of them.
Was my reaction really
that surprising?
Yes. It was.
Could you do what you did?
Of course you could.
But I never thought
you would, or could,
do that to me.
I'm really sorry, Kiddo,
but you thought wrong.
You and I have
unfinished business.
Baby.. you ain't kiddin'.
Pai Mei taught you
the Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique?
'Course he did.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know.
Because I'm
a bad person.
No.
You're not a bad person.
You're a terrific person.
You're my favorite person.
But every once in a while
you can be a real cunt.
How do I look?
You look ready.
Well, well, well.
If it ain't the little flower.
Good evening,
Mr. and Mrs. America
and all the ships at sea.
Let's go to press. Flash.
Do you have a magpie
in your home?
If you do,
you are most fortunate.
The magpie is the most
charming bird in all the world.
He is the best friend
a farmer ever had.
Treat him gently.
Treat him kindly.
And always remember,
the magpie deserves
your respect.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Now, I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I ain't got no headache.
Oh, yes, you have,
brother.
SubText: NoRMITA.326